# JOSE RIZALDY PALO

**&** 0436 281 268

0

ST MARYS NSW, 2760

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- Windows Applications testing
- Website Testing
- White Box Testing
- Black Box Testina
- Manual/Functional testina
- Finding Defects/issues
- Logging of Defects
- User Guide, Test Document creation
- Preparation and execution of Test Cases
- Provide IT support
- Perform code change/update

# EDUCATION & TRAINING

- 2011
   UST Global
   Associate Software
   Engineer Boot camp
- 2006-2011
   Mapua Institute of Technology,
   Philippines
   (BS Electronics & Communications Engineering)
- 2002-2006
   Casa Del Nino
   Science High School
   (Secondary School)

#### PERSONAL SUMMARY

Experienced and well talented IT professional with 7 years experience. Have specialised in Manual and Functional testing of Website and various Windows applications with an excellent attention to details, and have experience in Software development. Always willing to learn.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### IT SUPPORT / PROGRAMMER

Scientific Games - AUSTRALIA(January 2018 – May 2021)

Providing IT support, program enhancement, maintenance and Manual and Unit testing of Website and Windows application

#### Key Responsibilities

- Perform weekly/monthly client's server maintenance
- Code change /bug fix upon client's request (C#, VB 6.0)
- Perform code/issue investigation upon client's request
- Writing test cases and executing test steps
- Monitoring client's daily data
- Performing monthly maintenance of client's database
- Initiate automation testing using Selenium Web Driver

#### ACCOUNTS ADMINISTRATOR

BSA Itd Pty - AUSTRALIA (August 2017 – December 2017)

Worked as an account administrator and Quality assurance which regularly check the submitted photo evidence of field technicians to be eligible for payment

#### Key Responsibilities

- Check all the photo evidences from technician and asses if valid for payment
- Receive calls and answer clarifications from clients
- Data entry job

# JOSE RIZALDY PALO



0436 281 268



O ST MARYS NSW, 2760

### **TECHNOLOGIES**

- MS SQL Database
- TERADATA Database
- C#
- VB6.0
- Java / JavaScript
- JIRA / RQM / ClearQuest
- DataStage / Informatica

#### **AWARDS**

- Team of the Quarter (May - August 2016) -Teradata Philippines
- Team of the Quarter (July - September 2015) – Teradata **Philippines**

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Licences Electronics & Communications Engineer - Philippines
- Marketing Operations Certifications -**Philippines**
- Amazon Web Services **Philippines**
- Teradata 14 Certified Professional -**Philippines**

#### SOFTWARE QA / TESTER

Teradata – PHILIPPINES (March 2014 – June 2017)

I worked as an ETL, Database and Website tester (APRIMO). I worked as lead tester for internal project before becoming a SHAREPOINT 2016 administrator and a digital librarian for company's assets and IPs.

## Key Responsibilities

- Creating test cases and executing the test scripts
- Test documentation (Test case, Test result, bug/defect report)
- Bug Tracking and reporting
- Client interaction/meeting

# SOFTWARE QA / TESTER

UST Global Inc – PHILIPPINES (October 2012– March 2014)

I started working as a developer for a year before spending the rest of my career as a manual tester. Completed numerous testing (system integration, UAT, and regression testing) for client's website which is a big healthcare provider in America.

#### Key Responsibilities

- Creating test cases and executing the test steps Manually
- Test documentation (Test case, Test result, bug/defect report)
- Bug Tracking and reporting using bug tracking tools

# REFERENCES

Available upon request

#### **AVAILABILITY**

At least 3 week notice